

CONTACTS



+49 1793889148



zubova.alina@gmail.com

in <u>LinkedIn</u>



Köln, Germany



LANGUAGES

German B1 English B1

Russian Native speaker

SOFT SKILLS

Punctual, responsible - extensive experience in submitting reports on time while working as an accountant and auditor.

Self-sufficient, with an analytical mindset and high motivation to achieve a result - writing an audit plan, conducting an audit individually and in a group.

Easy and quick to learn - passed annual advanced training in audit, conducted regular monitoring of tax and legislative changes.

Sociable, easily joins the new team.

REASON FOR APPLYING FOR A JOB

Currently, I'm focused on extending my Functional testing skills and I'm interested in learning and implementation Automated Testing Skills. My priority goal is to obtain a position in a companythat offers a variety of challenging projects with growth potential in terms of individual and professional development.

I believe my relevant work experience provide me quality assurance and quality control skills

Portfolio: link GitHub

ALINA ZUBOVA

JUNIOR QA ENGINEER

HARD SKILLS

- Knowledge of software testing types, levels, test design techniques;
- Performing Requirements Analysis and Documentation Testing;
- Creation and execution of test cases, checklists, bug reports. Tools:
 Jira, Redmine, TestRail, Testlink, Confluence, Sitechko;
- Understanding the basics of web technologies: client-server architecture, HTTP/HTTPS, HTML/CSS (VSCode), <u>link GitHub</u> (DevTools, Fiddler);
- Understanding the basics of Rest API (Postman: run collections, using variables, managing environment; GET, POST request);
- Basic knowledge of Database: SQL gueries (select, join)

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

2021

- Course uTest Academy
- Course School for beginner testers software-testing.ru
- YouTube Course Tester From Scratch

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 uTest • Upwork • Participation in testing projects: Functional, Usability

2021 Practical work on a course project (School for beginner testers) Projects description: Testing of Web Application, Basic Knowledge of API. Functional, black box, smoke, ad hoc, GUI, exploratory testing. Creation of: Bug report, checklists, test cases.

Using Test Design Techniques (Equivalent partition, border Values)

Using Test Design Techniques (Equivalent partition, border Values) Test Analysis Techniques (Decision Table, State & Transition Testing)

Auditor

2008 – 2019 • LLC "Consulting agency "Territory leasing" • St. Petersburg, Russia

Participation in audits of companies of different forms of ownership and fields of activity. Audit of financial statements prepared in accordance with RAS. Writing reports and opinions on the results of inspections. Consulting on accounting and tax accounting issues.

Head Accountant

2003-2008 • CJSC "NEVOTREID" • St. Petersburg, Russia

Preparation of financial reports for subsequent submission to inspections and funds. Payroll, insurance premiums, preparation, and submission of reports to the Funds. Compilation and verification of primary accounting documentation.

Accountant

2002-2003 • CJSC "FC" Baltinvest "• St. Petersburg, Russia

Compilation and accounting of primary accounting documentation. Working with bank accounts of the organization. Preparation of accounting reports, accounting references. Registration of acts of reconciliation with debtors and creditors of the company. Registration and accounting of insurance contracts.

EDUCATION

2009 • Auditor • Saint Petersburg Trade and Economic Institute, Russia 1996–2002 Economist-manager • St. Petersburg Academy of Engineering and Economics, St. Petersburg, Russia